

Hi! — I'm a product designer with a background in front-end development. I'm particularly interested in **user experience, usability and research** and its applications to improve people's lives. My native language is **Spanish** and I'm fluent in **English**.

Experience

Product designer — Entrepreneur

EventNest

Oct 2024 — Present Spain — Remote

I am working on the creation of a **marketplace** that helps event organizers and promoters find the services they need to develop their activities. The project is currently in its initial phase, where I am conducting the necessary research to define the **MVP** (Minimum Viable Product) to begin working on.

Product designer — Entrepreneur

Geomites

Mar 2023 — Present Spain — Remote

I lead the UX and UI design of this project, where we are designing and developing a **mobile video** game for iOS and Android platforms in an agile environment.

Product designer — Freelance

Apr 2022 — Present Spain — Remote

I work as a product designer for different companies and sectors. My main freelance activities include designing and developing **company websites**, designing **corporate documents**, and participating in the **design process** of various products or services.

Marketing manager — Contract

Promam

Jul 2017 — Sep 2021 Spain — Onsite

I was responsible for marketing and design tasks, managing the design and development of the **company's website** and led **SEO** positioning campaigns. I spearheaded marketing campaigns on social media and organized and developed the design of various products necessary for the company's operations, including **catalogs, advertisements, and documents**. I also collaborated with stakeholders to organize the **marketing and sales strategy**.

Education

Google & Coursera, Interaction Design Foundation

2021 - Present

Design thinking: The ultimate guide, User Experience: Begginer's Guide, Foundations of User Experience, User research, Gestalt psychology, Human-Computer interaction, Design for the 21st century, Emotional design, Information visualization, Mobile user experience, Visual design, UI design patterns

Rey Juan Carlos University

Marketing degree

2011 - 2016

Skills

UX research, UX design, UI design, Wireframing, Prototyping, Problem solving, Communication, Design systems, Usability

Tools

Sketch, Figma, Adobe Creative suite, Framer, Webflow, Wordpress, HTML5, CSS3, Javascript, Axure, Asana, Jira, ChatGPT, Midjourney, NotebookLM

Contact

<u>alejandromorenomartin.com</u> +34 618110583 <u>alejandromorenomartin1990@gmail.com</u>